Welcome to the SHIELD Simularium - a cutting-edge, Virtual Reality environment.
(bowing in greeting) I am Iron Fist - Namaste.
Activating simulation.
Today’s replicated environment is modeled after my dojo in the mystic city of K’un-Lun.
There I defeated the dragon known as Shou-Lao the Undying, attaining the power of the IRON FIST.
Welcome, newbies and wanna-bees! Remember me? I’m Jennifer Walters but most people call me...
...She-Hulk. Congrats on making it this far!
Before we begin our training, we will demonstrate the full scope of our abilities. Like agility…
...And speed.
Don’t forget about strength...
Instructors! There’s a critical new development to report.
Going to full virtual mode - now.
The ROBS are transmitting live.
Our mission is paying off. A
fragment recovered from the Super
Adaptoid revealed the coordinates
of a secret HYDRA stronghold.
I’ve dispatched a small team to investigate. Meet Black Panther, one of our top trackers
The team’s in position.
We’ve confirmed that Red Skull and Madame Hydra are inside
Cloak that ROB before we’re made.
Just letting you know we’re here.
All clear. Where’s Wolverine?
Wake up Widow! This isn’t a training mission.
(sniffing) Panther’s back...
Perimeter guards neutralized. Has Vision finished scouting inside?
(with SWAT precision) He should be back in 3, 2...
There are five sentry
Adaptoids in the adjacent
corridor. They should not be a problem.
Follow me.
(exasperated) ...Or not This way.
Watch out. You’ve got company.
Everyone duck!
Nice toss
What’s our play?
Fall in
That’s not what that means
(whispering) The entire Adaptoid army appears to be offline
(stopping Cap) Well then don’t wake ‘em up
Vision, what’s your status?
(pointing) Trapped - in an energy field...
Get him outta there!
(disgusted) Ah, MODOK! Filthy beast!
Look there - in the shadows - Madame Hydra
- And Red Skull
Three of SHIELD’s most-wanted!
Move in!
(re Vision) This intruder’s presence tells us that SHIELD is close on our heels
This trap won’t hold him for long
We don’t need much time now. We’ll have them under our heels as soon as MY army is deployed
OUR army will be fully operational within the hour
Then we’ll eat SHIELD like a giant cupcake
It’s over, Red Skull
(turning, unconcerned) Only for the reign of Heroes
(pleasantly surprised) Oh? Captain America!
(growling) You are surrounded
Poor thing. Even your senses have deceived you this time
Come to MODOK!
What the -?
Holograms?!
(shouting right into lens) They’re coming for you! Get out!
Sorry to interrupt the broadcast but MODOK’s here. I see every one of you.
Jocasta! Your force-field!
Activating. Remain calm
Remain calm
You are completely safe
Oh yes, It’s very safe
All recruits - proceed through the exit to the transport corridor
Oh the corridor. Yes that’s very safe, says the mobile organism designed for killing!!
I’m going to kill you. That’s what I do.